zootout.com 2014-06-29

# 

Zootout Advertising Pvt. Ltd. owns & runs the website [ www.Zootout.com](http://www.zootout.com/), mostly called as Zootout. It assists people to find & share good food. This Privacy Policy is effective immediately for all users visiting Zootout & registering for personal accounts. Zootout is not bounded by any third party sites that may be linked to them, or any relationships you may have with the businesses listed on Zootout. 

This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of your information in connection with your use of our websites, emails, and mobile applications. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, a "user" is defined as someone using Zootout. To fulfil the purpose of our site, we need to display a limited amount of personal information, so that users are able to evaluate the trustworthiness of a particular shared experience. By using Zootout, you permit the collection and use of your personal information as outlined below in our Privacy Policy. You should visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Policy. The terms "we", "us", and "Zootout" refer to Zootout Advertising Pvt. Ltd. When you use the Site, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

By using Zootout or its applications (collectively, "Properties"), you are consenting to this Privacy Policy. 

## Disclaimers

Although we make efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy, we do not guarantee, warrant, represent, or promise such compliance.  

This Privacy Policy only applies to Properties we own or operate (solely or in conjunction with our partners). Any third-party websites linked from our Properties (for example, by banner advertisements) are governed by the privacy policies of the third parties that own and operate those websites. We have no control over third-party websites and assume no responsibility for their collection, use, disclosure, or protection of personal information.  

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time without prior notice to you. Please check back from time to time to review the current version. Your continued use of the Properties will indicate your acceptance of the new policy.  

The headings used throughout this Privacy Policy are meant to be illustrative of the subjects discussed under each heading and may not cover every topic identified in the heading. As a result, please read the Privacy Policy in its entirety.      

## Collection of Information

We may collect information from users of its Properties in various ways, including soliciting registration for use of our Properties. As part of such registrations, users may be required to submit personally identifiable information such as names, birthdates, photographs, and email addresses. The registration may require additional information, such as mailing addresses and phone numbers.  

Registrants may elect to receive our newsletters and third-party promotional materials. 

We may require registration for participation in special contests or sweepstakes. Special rules may apply to such contests or sweepstakes.   We may also collect information such as fictitious names, aliases, avatar identities, or any other form of fictitious identity in the event such identifiers can be and are created in connection with the Properties.  

From time to time, we may request information in connection with surveys or votes of users of our Properties. Surveys or votes may or may not require registration. Participation in such activities is voluntary.      

## Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Processes 

We may collect information from users of our Properties by using and accessing "cookies," "web beacons," "clear gifs," Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses, and other computer programs or processes. These programs or processes, such as for analytics, may also be used and accessed by third-party network advertisers or traffic measurement services.  

Cookies are small data files that are transferred to your computer by servers. Web beacons are small electronic images (usually single-pixel "gif" files) that allow access to cookies. Clear gifs are invisible electronic images. IP addresses are unique sets of numbers assigned to computers that are accessing the Internet.  

We, or the third parties, mentioned above, may use and access the computer devices in order to improve content offerings by, for example, tracking usage patterns, customizing content, and recording information submitted by users. However, the data will be aggregate and will not include personally identifiable information.  

If you wish, you may elect to configure your browser to prevent websites from installing and accessing cookies on your computer. Please note that blocking cookies will interfere with your use and enjoyment of the Properties. 

## Use of Information 

We collect information from registrants primarily to facilitate their participation in the Properties. Specifically, usernames and passwords allow registrants to access the Properties; and names and email addresses are helpful for communicating with registrants. The other information helps us to tailor the content of our Properties to user preferences and communicate information about other products or services that might be of interest. 

We may use your personally identifiable information in other ways in connection with our business; for example, we may use the information to alert you to improvements to the Properties and solicit your opinion about such improvements. 

We use non-personally identifiable information in an aggregate, anonymous manner primarily to (i) improve the design, functionality, and content of our Properties; and (ii) provide products and services that might interest our users. 

## Use of Links 

Zootout may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with those third parties, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.

## Personal data controlling 

To the extent you include personal information in your submissions (such as a photo of yourself), third parties may be able to identify you, and associate you with your user account, and contact you. Third parties can also associate you with your user account using the member lookup feature on Zootout. Please do not include information in your submissions that you expect to keep private. In addition, you can reduce the risk of being personally identified by choosing a fictitious account name, though doing so could detract from the credibility of your submissions. 

As a registered Zootout user, you can modify some of your personal information and your privacy preferences by accessing the "Account" section of this website. 

## Disclosure to Third Parties

We will usually not disclose any information about users of our Properties to any third parties. However, we may make disclosures from time to time in the following circumstances, without limitation: If you submit content for publication (for example, by sending an email or posting to a message board or chat room), then we may publish the content with any personally identifiable information that accompanies the content. 

  * Your user information may be displayed on the Properties to other users of the Properties (for example, your self-selected user name). 
  * If you voluntarily elect to receive information from a third-party vendor, we will forward that request to the vendor along with the personal information that you submit. 
  * We may disclose information in response to a court order or request of law enforcement personnel, or in connection with litigation or other legal proceedings. 
  * We may disclose information in the normal course of business with such third parties as (i) professional advisors; (ii) providers of technology, order fulfilment, or customer service assistance; or (iii) potential or existing affiliates, assignees, licensees, acquirers, or successors of our company. 
  * If we elect to disclose information to third parties that market products or services, co-brand services, or sponsor promotional events in connection with our users, users will have the option to opt out of such disclosure. In the event that we do disclose any such information to third parties, we typically require the third parties to maintain the confidentiality of the disclosed information. 

We maintain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access to private information in our possession. However, these procedures may not protect your information during transmission to our servers.

## Dispute Resolution 

If you face any trouble, or believe that Zootout has not adhered to any Privacy Policy, then you may write to Zootout at info@zootout.com. In your email, please describe in as much detail as possible ways in which you believe the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly.
